Next? Shall we go next? There are so many. So many people are coming.
From Fukushima Karaoke List. You are our listener, aren't you?
I have a question for Ano-chan, the artist.
What did you think of Pekopa's major label debut song, Earth?
Did you hear it? Let's listen to it.
Haven't heard it yet? I haven't listened to it for today.
Eww. Get off of me.
You warmed me up. I started to feel like I knew that song when you played it.
What? What made you do it? Well, I've been playing in bands and writing original songs for a long time.
I had been writing original songs for a long time, and we were going to release one of our songs at a solo show, and the person who heard it said it was a really good song, so why don't we put it in a van?
Well, it's not a van, it's on the web, and it's now available digitally, but I'd like to hear it for that reason.
I didn't think it would come to this, but it did.
Jakesha, you're so cool.
Nurse, this planet is on the verge of collapse.
No, I'm not in love with it.
Narsed void. It's still there. It can't be erased.
No, you don't have to erase it.
Land, sea, and skyline. It's a dirty planet, full of trunks.
Hmm, it's tainted.
You're listening to me right there.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Wish!
Roast pork cutlet with ponzu!
Gal King's skin, ego and dirafi on the sleigh panel.
Gal-Oh's least favorite word is betrayal
Mystery
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh... *
What do you think?
Good.
Oh!
I'm so happy.
I don't know...
The artist
You just sontac'd me, didn't you?
No, you know what?
I thought Melo was really great.I really thought Melo was so much better, and now I think it's
That's great.
thank you so much!
It's great.
The way the chorus opens up
It's like it opens up with a "poof".
I love how it starts with "earth".
But the lyrics
Roast pork cutlet
Loin tonkatsu is served with ponzu sauce
The lyrics are a bit
It's a joke, right?
I'm really trying to write them.
I thought the way I sang it was a bit weird.
I thought it was the coolest way to sing.
The melody is good, and the chorus is refreshing, but
But you stop at the beginning of the first verse.
I get it.
Earth, what's today's star?
I'm going to play that today.
I'll think it's a joke.
I might stop.
But really, I get that a lot.
They say, "The lyrics are good, but you should do something about the lyrics and the way you sing.
That's true.
I can sing normally if I want to.
But if I did, it wouldn't have any personality.
That's fine, but what about the lyrics?
The lyrics are just random, right?
They're not appropriate.
I mean, you know, energy issues...
I'm going to put some energy issues in the lyrics.
It's called "Gal Ono Hadas Solar Pare Eco Yalilafi.
He said it.
I heard "Yalilafi.
That's not an ear.That wasn't an ear.
That wasn't an ear.
Maybe I should think about the lyrics a little more.
It's okay.
It's fine, but it's not where you want it to go.
That's a fair point.
But I was really surprised that it was so much better than I thought it would be.
I really was.
Did Shupei sing this?
I mean, this is the part where he sings "Lawston Katsouwer" and stuff.
I didn't actually know the lyrics to the song.
And then he said, "I'm going to record it.
I don't know, I heard it once.
Then I said, "Sing this.
I sang it.
I didn't put any of my heart into it.
Well, I've already asked him to sing with me.
So maybe next time Shupei can write the lyrics and I can write the music.
That's a good idea.
I'm a pretty good singer.
I'm gonna have a cup of tea.
No kidding.
Wait a minute, I'm doing it right, too.
I was going to get a buzz last time, but I didn't get any.
Next up is Mochimaru from Tokyo.
Anochan-sensei, Pecopa seems to be having some trouble lately. Please listen to her and give her some advice.
Yes?
What? Is he troubled?
Is something bothering you?
I'm just...
I've been pooping a lot.
I don't know why.
But...
I poop about 5 times a day.
Isn't that healthy?
I'm kind of waiting for the poop...There was a bit of a poop wait and everything...
I don't know why...
I was at a talk show the other night, and about a minute before the show was about to start.
I thought I had to pee.
I sat down to pee.
I sat down to pee, and the poop came out first.
I thought I could make it on the pee scale.
I thought I could make it on the pee scale, but the poop scale was rushed, so...
So I was a little late.
And when the opening came out...
They'd make fun of the fact that I was pooping.
I had to tell them why I was late.
I think he ate a lot of food.
Are they eating?
Is he eating a lot?
But I've already done it three times.
But he's already done it three times.
That's unusual, isn't it?
Is there something wrong?
Maybe you ate a lot of food that's easy to digest.
Is that what's going on?
Yes, that's what I meant.
That thing?
Burdocks?
Yeah.
The fiber thing?
You know, I've got five cameras rolling right now.
Can you please not waste the media?
It's eating up a lot of gigs already.
Yeah, I know.
You should go to the hospital.
Maybe you should go to the hospital.
Maybe you should get a physical.
You should get a physical.
Yeah.Yeah.
I'm going to the hospital.
What's wrong with you?
My problem?
The kind I can fix.
I don't know.
It's a problem.
Trouble.
You have a unique way of dressing, Ano.
I'm not that interested in clothes.
She thinks I don't have any sense of style.
But now that I have a cool sense of style.
I'm already seen as someone with no taste.
I can't be fashionable anymore.
I'm ahead of you?
Yeah, because he's basically a dork.
Because he's basically a dork.
There's got to be a way to get rid of that.
I've never seen him in casual clothes.
Oh, here he is.
What do you think? It's good.
I mean, your face is awful.
I mean, your face... that's the face you make when you walk your dog.
What is this?
Is it bad?
Is this what you wear when you get dressed up?
If I posted an instagram of me going for a walk, they'd be like.
It's like, "Oh my God, that's not good.
I'm just going for a walk.
The hat and the bottoms... and the top too?
I don't know... the same ones.
It's weird and creepy.
Weird?
What was it?
M...
Marines.Marines.
Not Matsui's.
It's not Matsui's M.
Did you put Matsui's M on it?
It's "M" for Marines.
Don't worry about the dog.
I'm not worried about the dog.
Don't come back!
I really don't think he'll recognize me.
Walk down the street.
They won't recognize me. They say I don't have a celebrity aura.
I didn't think people would say I looked so dorky.
It's normal, right?
It's normal in my opinion.
I don't know why people say that.
Maybe I should narrow down the genre.
Genre?
Decide what you want to wear.
By genre, do you mean hoodies?
Hoodie style or street style?
If you start out with a broad range of fashion and end up with this...
That's fine, but you'll end up with this.
I'd like that one too.
American zine.
What?
Amecazin?
What's Amecazin look like?
Farewell, Mr. Monitor.
No, no, no, not like that?
Then no.
What is "Americanzine"?
But there's one genre I'd like you to wear, Sean Angel.
Tell me about it.
Punk.
Punk? I mean, old school.
Like the old L'Arc‾an style.Like a L'Arcueen look.
It looks tacky when worn now.
But I like people who go all the way around and make a fashion statement.
But it's a little bit like that.
That kind of thing.
But I used to really wear that kind of thing.
So I think I'd look good in it.
A slim black one with a chain.
But the chain...
Once, when I was waiting for the train at the station.
I was sitting on a bench
I was sitting on the bench.
The chain got stuck in the gap between the bench and the fence.
I was about to get on the train when it came.
But it got stuck.
I couldn't get on.
I can't get on even though there's an open seat.
Kukk, kukk, kukk...
But there's so many people getting off the train.
He's got his chain caught on the chair.
People think I'm a dork, but I usually just ride through like this.
As a result, I'm late for my part-time job.
But I'll give it a try.
That's deep.
Thank you very much.
But, Matsui-san...
I'm actually not so good with chains.
I used to wear a winter scarf.
A long scarf.
Long scarves are cool, aren't they?
But me...
I saw Matsui-san's long scarf.
Matsui-san stood up from his chair.
He was wearing a long scarf.
Then, I don't know if he peed or what.
I don't know why, but there's a long scarf coming out of here.Somehow there's a long muffler coming out of here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's a muffler!
Matsui-san, there's a muffler coming out of your crotch.
No?
I made a mistake.
I put them on in the wrong order.
I put on my pants last.
I thought it was Nakada.
I thought it was Nakada's Milano Collection.
Nakata's been here a long time, but he didn't start from here.
From the airport.
It's like the exit of a long muffler is here.
I'll try some fashion when I hit Anochan.
Hey, go on location.
Don't do it once.
I'll be on this show.
Let's do it on Ano-chan.
That's good.
Will you go shopping with me, Ano-chan?
I wanted you to wear it, right?
That's fine... even though it's chained.
It's fine.
People will probably say that's tacky.
I don't like that.
No, no, no.
It's just a project to get Ano to coordinate with you.
This is the most unreasonable part of fashion.
If I did it voluntarily...
I'd be like, "Wow, Ms. Matsui, you're so lame.
But if I asked Ano-chan to think of it and put it up on the website
I'm sure you have a good sense of style.
Even though it's the same outfit.
It depends on who picked it out.
People are looking at you.People are looking at you.
They don't look at the clothes themselves.
They're looking at who's doing it.
That's how the world works.
There's an All Night Nippon corner with Pecopa.
"Quiz Matsuidera-san" on Pecopa's All Night Nippon corner.
Let's do it.
Remember the quiz Matsuidera-san?
What was it?
I remember.
The listeners would come up with a question that they thought Matsuidera would say, and I'd come up with my own answer.
And then I'd think about what I was going to say, and I'd say it was right or wrong.
The plan was to come up with the correct and incorrect answer.
You mean we're supposed to guess what Matsuidera will say?
Is that what you mean this time?
I understand.
Positive words.
I'll have them put on their headphones.
Here you go.
Matsuidera-san.
I can't hear you.
Hello?
Okay, let's start with the first one.
The event before the event.
Time to make two in the morning
I kissed the tip of your innocent nose
I kissed the tip of your nose
Good night, sir.
Really quiet. I thought you'd come at least one more time. Comedy-wise, you know.
I'm just curious.
Shut up.
I'm trying to do it right now.
Morning Musume。 It's on.Morning Musume。 It's playing.
It's not karaoke.
I'll be quiet.
From Shizuoka Prefecture, Kohoku Onitan.
As you grow up and the environment around you changes, is there one belief that you cannot change?
Yes.
Do you have any?
I have to think about this, don't I, Shinobu Matsuo?
It is difficult.
If it were me.
If it were me. Oh, okay.
Normally, people would say, "This and that will never change," but if it were Shinobu Matsuo, he would say, "Growth and change is what human beings believe in.
He would say that.
Don't you think he would say that?
I think he would say that money is everything.
Really?
It's over?
It's over.
Now we have a question like this. We have already thought about how Shinobu Matsuo would answer.
As you grow up and as your surroundings change, is there any one belief that you cannot compromise or change?
Yes, I do.
Oh, that was quick.
Yes, please ask Shinobu Matsuo.
I wonder what he would say.
I think it is a mind that accepts my changing self.
Close.
Close?
But it is our belief in growing and changing.
The content is almost the same.
That's great.
Well, Shupenon-san.
As long as you have money, everything is good.
I don't know if I'd say that.
I don't know if I'm going to say it.
I'm not going to say it, but I'm going to say it.I always say, "I don't know why you would say that" or "I don't know why you would say that," and then I say it.
I always say, "From here, I'm not going to say it," but I always give an unaccustomed "tskk" when I would normally say "No, I'm not going to say it.
It's short. It might be the shortest one.
That's why Anochan is here.
She's amazing.
But the way she said it was romantic.
Yes, yes, yes. I thought that's the way he said it.
No, that's great.
One more thing.
Sorry, Shun-san, I was thinking in Matsuo's direction.
You can't do that. Matsuo would certainly say something like that.
You do say that.
You did say that. You did say it, the second time.
That's great.
Great job.
The office of the president.
This is Sayu from Tokyo, Japan.
I have been in a position of leading junior staff at my workplace this year, and I am struggling with how to do my job every day.
I am especially concerned about teaching simple things to the older juniors who joined the company as mid-career hires, because I feel it would be rude to do so.
And I can't speak well.
I think that in the entertainment industry, seniority is prioritized over age,
If you have any advice on how to get along with older juniors, please let me know.
I see.
Yes, I do.
Yes, there is indeed.
Is there anyone? Yes, you do.
Me?
But I still don't have a concept of my artistic career,
I don't have the average number of years in the past,
I use a slang expression when people call me "Anochan",
That's true.
Isn't this a lot of comedians?
There are a lot of comedians. That's true.
How are you doing? What do you do?
If I'm close with someone who is older and younger than me, it's really a senior/junior relationship. Even if they are older than me.
But this is a little strange, but with Yoshimoto comedians, it is a little different,But this is a little strange, but with the Yoshimoto comedians, it is a little different,
For example, the two guys from New York are older than me, but they are my juniors. For example, the two guys from New York are older than me, but they are my juniors.
But I call him Shimasa-san, and I call him Yashiki-san.
It's not a hassle.
I don't want Shuhei to think that I'm acting like a senior,
Mei-hyun-san is also a junior, but he is older than me, so I call him Mei-hyun-san.
I'm doing this to maintain a good relationship with him.
That's right.
But how would Songinji say it?
Mr. Songinji?
No, look at me. Most of them are younger than me.
I'm willing to take a licking. So let's be fair.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, if it's Shoinji.
No, no. Anything is possible if you do it by force.
We'll screw them over with force. Not bad.
You too, Matsui.
Okay, here we go. I'll go with this.
Okay, Sasada.
OK.
Now, Matsuin Tsukasa. I'm from Tokyo Left Sanitation.
Thank you very much.
I have been in a position to teach junior staff at my workplace this year, and I am struggling to know how to teach them my job every day.
I would like to know if you have any advice on how to get along with older juniors.
I know that comedians in particular have this problem.
Yes, there are. I am sure that this is a problem in many industries and in many societies, but I understand that you are struggling with it.
I see.
We have made a plan for how you would say this.
We have? What I might say? Yes, we have. Yes, please!
I don't know how to say it, but within a company, the company's history is important,
I want you to treat me as a senior, confident that I can do the job better than the older juniors.
However, once you step out of the company, I think it is okay to reverse the relationship between senior and junior as a human being.
Thank you very much.
If that ruffles your feathers, you can always use force to screw them over.
The owner of the company, Mr. Doshu pair, is right.
Screw 'em with force.You can do anything you want if you do it by force.
If you do it by force, you can do anything.
And you, Ano, you're like, "Let's be fair.
So in the end, we're gonna have to use force.
Isn't that great?
That's right.
Don't say that.
Don't say it right away.
I can do air violence.
I can do air violence. I can do air violence.
I'm gonna do some air violence, like the kind I like.
I'll do it.
What are you doing?
I'm not hurting anyone.
I'm not hurting myself.
This is air violence.
Oh my God!
There are people like this in front of stations.
That's Mr. Matsui.
That's not me.
That's Matsui-san.
I don't usually recognize him.
But that's great, that's your partner.
Last question!
Last question.
This is Matsui-san's again.
Just a normal question.
From Shiga Prefecture, from the "Kitani-ha" group
How do you deal with cockroaches when you are alone in your house?
Surprise!
Watch out!
That scared the hell out of me!
Oh, come on.Hey, don't do that.
What if it comes out?
I'll take him down.
I can deal with it or something.
No, it's disgusting.
I'm a cockroach.
I'm okay with cockroaches.
I mean, I'd be so surprised if they put something like this out there.
I can handle cockroaches.
It's okay, I can see them now.
This is disgusting.
It's a little creepy.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
What's this?
Disgusting! Disgusting!
That's disgusting.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Where is it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Rats are cute!
I'd get so excited if I saw one on the street.
I mean, it's got a real tail.
It's still a little bit realistic.
What's wrong with you?
I'm exhausted.
You're tiring me out.
What are you going to do when it comes out?
What do you do when it comes out?
What are you going to use?
A box cutter.
I've never been in a house before.
I've never been home.
You know, at my part-time job.
I was working, and I had to unlock the door.
I came in early.I got there early.
I got caught in a rat trap.
I couldn't get in for a long time.
I ran to the stairs.
I said, "What should I do?
And then a rescue guy came to me.
He did the pattern...
I was like, "Geez!" and we were both like, "Oh my God!
But thanks to him...
But thanks to him, we got in.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand to see you like this.
Are you okay?
Bugs.
I don't know about bugs, though.
Spiders are weird.
What's that?
I don't want to touch it.
Spiders are fine.
What the hell are you doing? I'm talking to you.
Don't do it. Please don't do it.
Don't do it.
I don't think so.
Oh, no?
I really can't.
You've got to fix this.
If there are cockroaches in the house...
No, cockroaches in the first place.
Is that what I think it is?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's just a regular geek.
But that's okay.
But bugs... in general...
They call them pests.
But from their point of view...
We're the biggest pest of all.We're the biggest pests of all.
Let's hold each other's reinforcing battles. Let's hold each other's reinforcing battles.
I think we'd be more scared of them than they are of us.
You're right... they're that big.
That's why...
You should apologize.
I'm going to cry.
Thank you for sending in your questions.
Well, next time...
I'm going to buy your clothes.
Let's go on location one last time.
Let's go on location for the last time.
The three of us will go shopping in Harajuku.
After that, I'd like to go to Nezumi's zoo.
Why? We don't have a zoo.
Let's walk around Shibuya at night and find rats.
I hate this time of year!
It's getting warmer, I hate this time of year!
I've found a mouse!
I'll do it till I find a mouse.
No, no, no, no!
I know where they are.
Subscribe to our channel!